<resources>
    <string name="app_name">my projects</string>
    <string name="newscontent"> "Rohit Sharma stood tall amidst a collapse and then attacked his way to a hundred in the format, making him the first to make five hundreds in men's T20Is.He later turned up with the bat in the Super Over in the tied game with India needing 17 to win and smashed two sixes. But the Super Over was tied too with Rohit retiring hurt on the fifth ball to bring a quicker runner in. India went on to win the second Super Over with Rohit smashing a six and a four.Glenn Maxwell, Suryakumar Yadav and Rohit himself had four hundreds in the format prior to this game.In India's final T20I before the ICC Men's T20 World Cup, Rohit made a strong statement with a career-best 121*, helping India to a score past 200 despite the early collapse. Rinku, meanwhile, finished unbeaten on 69, with three successive sixes to end the innings.

The final over saw 36 runs being scored with five sixes, taking India to a total of 212/4.The unbeaten 190-run stand between Rohit and Rinku is the highest for India in men's T20Is. Afghanistan matched India's score with Gulbadin Naib's spectacular 23-ball 55*, but in the Super Over, Rohit fired again to make it another tie.He returned to hit a six and a four in the second Super Over as India sealed a win and 3-0 series victory.Rohit, who made a return after more than a year to T20Is for this series, had made ducks in the first two games of the series, but turned it around spectacularly on Tuesday with a hundred off 64 balls.

India were reeling at the beginning of the innings after opting to bat first with Yashasvi Jaiswal (4), Virat Kohli (0), Shivam Dube (1) and Sanju Samson (0) all falling cheaply."</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
</resources>